Is Jung Ji-eun's notable works
her Instagram?
Think it through.
That's all for today's live stream.
The company has decided to give you
a final 2 weeks for observation.
Up till midnight on June 6.
The target KPI is
sales of 10 billion KRW.
A mini album.
We will produce and release one
in 2 weeks.
Ji-eun.
Can I kiss you?
[Broadcast channel
live stream interview]
Ji-eun.
This is your first time joining us
for an exclusive
group interview, right?
Yes.
Yes. Please look after me.
Don't be too nervous.
Just take it as a chat between friends.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Okay. Three, two, one. Action.
Hello. I am today's host, Song Minah.
Today, we've invited
Wonder-X's third member,
Jung Ji-eun.
I heard you've been preparing a new song.
Yes.
We're preparing a mini album.
All of our members are doing their best.
Yes.
We are working very hard
on preparing this mini album.
[When are we going to see the disbandment news article?
I think Jung Ji-eun would be better off going solo.
Can this girl group even keep going?
Are the fans doing okay? The members look so awkward with each other.
What is up with Jung Ji-eun's expression?
How much longer can Wonder-X last? When are we finally going to see the disbandment news?
Looking at Jung Ji-eun's face, her heart clearly isn't in it anymore.
This isn't going to be their last livestream, is it?
What is the agency's stance on this? It looks like Wonder-X is finished.]
Please look forward to it.
Thank you.
Okay. Practice must be tough.
You must be stressed as a new member too.
It's stressful,
but with Yebin and Minah's help,
I've been pushing through.
Recently,
there has been talk about
Wonder-X's disbandment on the internet.
Wonder-X will not disband.
You look very sure.
Yes.
We cherish each other
a lot.
Yebin is always protecting us quietly.
Minah also
works very hard.
I'm also very happy
to be able to join Wonder-X.
No matter what happens,
we will never be apart.
Yes.
Let's move on to the next segment.
It's the Q&A session.
Ji-eun, pick one.
The first note.
Is Jung Ji-eun's notable works
her Instagram?
O-Our group has many other notable works.
Please look forward to more in the future.
Next question.
One of the biggest controversies
surrounding Jung Ji-eun
is how she parachuted into the group.
There are many people
who are questioning
why she got the chance.
We would like to hear what Jung Ji-eun
has to say about this.
[Is Kang Yebin in love with Jung Ji-eun? She definitely likes her, haha.
Whoa, did you see that just now? What was with that look Kang Yebin gave her?
Wait, no way, right? Kang Yebin's aura is insane.]
Since starting my career as an idol,
I've foreseen
that I'd be asked questions like this.
We're just ordinary girls.
But we keep living in bad comments.
Those who are watching this,
think about
how rude this question was.
That's all for today's live stream.
[This is like watching a movie. Kang Yebin's expression is so serious.
The look in Kang Yebin's eyes has totally changed. Whoa, what is the deal between those two?
There is definitely something going on between them. Yebin-unnie is insanely cool!]
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Bin.
Thank you so much for today.
Don't say that.
I just did what I should do as a leader.
But
you did a good job today.
You were very calm.
But
will the fans
be disappointed to hear that?
I care about your feelings
more than the fans'.
More importantly,
I just want you to be happy.
It's great
with you here.
Let's go.
We have to go to the company.
Hello.
Get in the car first.
Thank you.
Your shoulders are wet.
Let me put a blanket on you.
The heater is on.
Bin.
Mm?
Thank you for today.
If it weren't for you,
something bad would've happened.
The person who wrote that question
was the one in the wrong.
You were really cool today.
I almost fell for you.
I'm also
really happy to be on a show with you.
Your hands are cold.
Is it better now?
Yes.
It's nice.
Ji-eun.
Can I kiss you?
I've always wanted to say this.
You've worked hard
through this journey.
This is the company's final decision.
It was a difficult decision.
Thank you for your hard work
for this period of time.
The company has decided to give you
a final 2 weeks for observation.
Up till midnight on June 6.
The target KPI is
sales of 10 billion KRW.
If you don't hit
the target sales within this time frame,
we'll follow our original plan
and disband Wonder-X.
10 billion KRW?
We've just exceeded 5 billion KRW
with all our sales
accumulated since our debut.
This is
really the final chance.
I believe you can do it.
We can do it.
This was a difficult decision.
Let me make this clear:
popularity and buzz—
they are both double-edged swords.
Don't think you can get applause
just by working hard.
What follows might be
more sharp criticism and condemnation—
and even malicious attacks.
Yebin and Minah are experienced,
so they can get through it.
But this target is different from before.
Ji-eun especially—
you need to be mentally prepared.
Determination is not enough.
You need a strong heart.
All right.
I'll stop here.
Come on, tell me:
how are you going
to hit 10 billion KRW?
A mini album.
We will produce and release one
in 2 weeks.
Two weeks?
How is that possible?
How can you say that's impossible
before even trying?
Ji-eun can compose,
I will write the lyrics,
and Minah can be the visual.
We can reach 10 billion KRW...
in 2 weeks.
[Evaluation Report]
[Rookie girl group Wonder-X's debut preparation and evaluation]
This won't work.
This melody is too ordinary.
Shall we take a break?
Bin.
We don't have time to rest.
Shall I play for you?
Huh?
This is...
The song you wrote for me
in our high school freshman year—
do you remember?
The title...
Was it "Scandal Love"?
I was serious
back then, though.
I remember now.
I'm exhausted.
The school club is too tiring.
Should I just quit?
Why did you bring your guitar?
Bin.
Yeah?
I wrote a song.
Really?
You?
Can you play it for me?
Quick!
The song is called
"Scandal Love."
It's not that it's a great song.
Don't laugh after hearing it.
Why would I laugh at you?
Play it for me, quick!
Ji-eun.
Is the "Love" in this song
me?
Yeah.
Ji-eun, listen carefully.
You’re my future composer—
my exclusive producer.
We will reach the top.
So we won't give up.
Understand?
I think the chorus
can be repeated another time.
Okay.
Let me think about the lyrics.
Use this.
Are you fighting a pencil?
Thank you,
Jin.
Normally, I'd fight my pencil
if I can't solve some equations.
That's right.
I've seen that.
Does that mean
you've been watching me do my homework?
Yes.
You look like the heroine of a comic book
when you're studying hard.
What are you talking about?
What comic protagonist?
Are you pulling my leg?
Yes.
Let the pencil off
next time you get it wrong.
So
you always look at me when I study?
Yes.
You look like the heroine of a comic book
when you're studying hard.
What are you talking about?
Are you pulling my leg?
But
the comic protagonist
needs some encouragement.
Ms. Ji-eun,
can you teach me
how to solve this question?
Sure.
I'll teach you once.
Teach me.
Quick!
Wonder-X...